<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="faq_key1">1）Pure MiLi on the phone system and Bluetooth?</string>
    <string name="faq_value1">1 IOS system: IOS7 above, Bluetooth 4 above; Android \n2. system: Android 4.3 or above, Bluetooth 4. </string>
    <string name="faq_key2">2）Pure MiLi how to connect with the phone?	</string>
    <string name="faq_value2">1.Touch of Mili pure switch at the bottom of the. At this time equipment LED lights flashing; \n2. open mobile phone mili pure app (confirm Bluetooth phone system is open, please do not use this connection device, Bluetooth 4.0 without the need to be matched connected directly open the app connected devices can be); \ N3. For the first time into Bluetooth selection page, click mili signal bound (app that Bluetooth has been connected, equipment LED lights Changliang). Follow up, the device automatically bind the mobile app, if the replacement of equipment re select the binding can be.</string>
    <string name="faq_key3">3）Pure MiLi how to use?</string>
    <string name="faq_value3">1.Will cap as shown in the direction of rotation, unscrew the cap; \ N 2. Touch the bottom of the device switch, open the phone app connection. \ N3. When the tips Bluetooth connection is successful, the metal probe vertically attached to a part to be detected about 5S; \n4. please ensure the metal probe effective contact with the skin, after the completion of the test, data analysis results will be shown on the phone.</string>
    <string name="faq_key4">4）Why the product indicator light has been flashing?</string>
    <string name="faq_value4"> If the device is turned on, the product indicator has been flashing, said the Bluetooth connection is not successful, please try to restart the Pure MiLi, and confirmed that the mobile phone has been turned on.</string>
    <string name="faq_key5">5）What is the skin moisture reference value?	</string>
    <string name="faq_value5" formatted="false">Accounted for%2s%%</string>
    <string name="faq_value10" formatted="false">Hand: 30% ~ 38% \n face: 32% ~ 42% \n eyes: 35% ~ 45% \n neck: 35% ~ 45%</string>
    <!-- <string name="faq_value5"> 手部：%30.～38%%	\n脸部：32%%rr.～42%%rr.	\n 眼部：35%%rr.～45%%rr.	\n 颈部：35%%rr.～45%%rr.	</string> -->
    <string name="faq_key6">6）Pure mili how to activate and guarantee?	</string>
    <string name="faq_value6">Mili series products within one year warranty from the date of purchase, Shenzhen Harry Tong Industrial Co., Ltd. bear all the materials and workmanship caused problems, a n buyers need in the purchase of products, from 7 days to company official website, online activate the warranty.</string>
    <string name="faq_key7">7）How to contact us?</string>
    <string name="faq_value7">If you have any questions in the course of using the product, please contact us immediately, thank you for your \n domestic email:customerservice@hali-power.com \nDomestic web site：www.myMiLi.cn\nForeign e-mail:cs@hali-power.com\nForeign website：www.myMiLi.com\n				</string>

</resources>